purekana.com 2019-08-28

# Official Pure Kana Privacy Policy | Purekana

Last Updated on May 24, 2018. PureKana respects your privacy rights and is committed to protecting the information we collect from you online.

This Privacy Policy is effective immediately for users on or after May 25, 2018 and will become effective on May 25, 2018 for users that already obtain services from us. To review our previous privacy policy, please click <https://purekana.com/old-privacy-policy/>.

This website is operated by PureKana. By visiting our site and/ or purchasing from us, you engage in our “Service”. This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use, and disclosure of information about you in connection with your use of our Services, including those offered through our website, emails, and mobile applications (collectively, the "Service"). Throughout the site, the terms “we”, “us” and “our” refer to PureKana. PureKana offers this website, including all information, tools and services available from this site to you, the user. PureKana is an Arizona corporation with its headquarters in Los Angeles, California. In addition, PureKana LTD operates from Watford, Hertz, United Kingdom WD244YY. When you use the Service, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.

## **TABLE OF CONTENTS**

  1. ### INFORMATION WE COLLECT, HOW WE COLLECT IT AND HOW WE USE IT

  2. ### METHODS OF COLLECTING INFORMATION

  3. ### USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

  4. ### WEB TECHNOLOGIES

  5. ### THIRD PARTIES

  6. ### TO OPT OUT OF THIRD-PARTY TRACKING ON OUR WEBSITE USE THE FOLLOWING TOOLS

  7. ### CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL DATA

  8. ### DATA RETENTION AND ACCOUNT TERMINATION

  9. ### NO INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM CHILDREN

  10. ### SECURITY

  11. ### MANAGE ACCURATE INFORMATION

  12. ### INTERNATIONAL USERS

  13. ### CONTACT

  14. ### MODIFICATIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

  15. ### CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS: YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

### **1.INFORMATION WE COLLECT, HOW WE COLLECT IT AND HOW WE USE IT**

We may collect and store information about you in connection with your use of the Service, including any information you transmit to or through the Service. We use that information to provide the Service’s functionality, fulfill your requests, improve the Service’s quality, engage in research and analysis relating to the Service, personalize your experience, track usage of the Service, provide feedback to third party businesses that are listed on the Service, display relevant advertising, market the Service, provide customer support, message you, back up our systems, enhance the security of the Service, and comply with legal obligations. Even when we do not retain such information, it still must be transmitted to our servers initially and stored long enough to process.  
Specifically, we may collect the following information:

• Your name, addresses, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, date of birth, username, password and other personally identifiable information;  
• Certain financial or demographic profile information to be used in the aggregate, such as your age, gender, purchase history, interests, zip/postal code or country. Demographic information is not considered personal information unless it is linked to personal information about a specific user;  
• Service provider name and the date, time and content of any messages sent from you to us;  
• IP address and other technical information collected from the servers utilized by you or your vendors, such as information and data that is automatically collected upon visiting the Website (i.e., webpage http headers (home server domain names, internet protocol address, operating system type, browser type and language) and user-specific or aggregate information on what pages you access on the Website). Technical information is not considered personal information unless it is linked to personal information about a specific user;  
• Credit/debit card and other billing information, including cardholder transaction data, card numbers, expiration dates, billing addresses and CVV codes;  
• Information provided on any application (including the App) or authorization and any other information you or your mobile device provides to us;  
• Information regarding uses of the services; and  
• Other information provided to us in any way, shape or form.

### **2\. METHODS OF COLLECTING INFORMATION**

We may collect information in one or more of the following ways:  

  * Through the completion of electronic forms found on the Website or on a third party-hosted website, whether via computer or mobile device;
  * Through the completion of paper forms provided to us;
  * Through SMS (Short Message Service) messages sent via cell phone, or through e-mail and other communications;
  * Through telephone calls made to us, or vice versa;
  * Through surveys;
  * Through referring websites or third parties, including social media sites such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, YouTube, Google+ and others;
  * Through the maintenance and analysis of Website server logs; and
  * Via “cookies” (small text files placed by us on your computer(s)), single pixel GIF image files (also called “Web beacons”), Website server log analysis and other similar technological means.
  * Certain portions of the Website may require that you register for an Account before being able to access them. On those portions of the Website that require registration, we may collect information to create your account, as well as to determine specific content, products and services that may be of particular interest to you. By collecting and maintaining accurate information, we learn more about your interests and needs and are better able to provide you with such content and with offers for such products and services.

**3\. USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION**

We may use the information we collect to identify the parties with whom we are dealing and to provide customized information and offers of products and services. We currently use third party services that display customized content and advertising provided by us. We may use the information for statistical and/or marketing purposes, to improve our technologies, to provide information about our company and to deliver advertising and promotional information from our partners and third party vendors. We may track your use of the Website over time for the purpose of, among other things, enhancing your experience on the Website and providing marketing messages, promotions, offers of products and services and other content which we think may be of specific interest to you.  
We reserve the right to share, rent, sell or otherwise disclose the information we collect from you to third parties. We may also share your information with certain third parties in other circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm and/or ensuring the security of our network and services. We may also use the information you provide to market products and services to you. We may obtain your information through third parties by virtue of advertisements placed by us on websites maintained by those third parties. We will collect and/or share certain of your information with third parties for the purposes of fulfilling orders for products or services placed by you and for providing you with newsletters or other communications. We may also use information provided by you to manage your Account.  
We may store or transfer your credit/debit card data in order to more easily provide services to you. If such credit/debit card and other billing information is collected and/or stored, such credit/debit card and other billing information will be collected and transferred over a secure connection in accordance with applicable regulatory requirements, and is used only for processing underlying transactions. We will share this information only with those directly involved in the processing of the underlying transaction, and who maintain appropriate security measures designed to safeguard such information.  
When we use third parties to assist us in collecting and/or processing your personal information, we typically request that they comply with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. However, we make no representation or warranty that such third parties will comply with any such request.  
We may provide you with direct access to functionality from other third parties, including Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, YouTube, Spotify, advertising networks and others. The placement of social media widgets, or advertising units on the Website may permit these third parties to see information about you and your activities via cookies, web beacons and other technologies they place and/or access on your browser or device, even if you do not interact with them.  
We may add your information to our databases to contact you through future e-mails, postal mailings and SMS text-messaging regarding site updates, upcoming events, new products and services and/or the status of orders placed online. We use geolocation for purposes of tracking location when our Website is used and in order to better target product and service offerings and other information to our users.  
We reserve the right to release information to law enforcement or other governmental officials as we, in our sole discretion, deem necessary to comply with applicable law.  
Please also note:  

a. Account Information: If you create an account with PureKana, we may store and use the information you provide during that process, such as your full name, email address, zip code, physical address, and other information you may provide with your account, such as your gender, phone number, and birth date. We may publicly display your first name and last initial, or other content you submit through the registration process, as part of your account profile. You can modify some of the information associated with your account through your account settings. Alternatively, you may contact us directly to do so by emailing: info@purekana.com. If you believe that someone has created an unauthorized account depicting you or your likeness, you can request its removal by flagging it.

b. Public Content: Your contributions to the Service left in the comments sections on our Website are intended for public consumption and are therefore viewable by the public, including your ratings, reviews, collections. Your account profile is not public. You may contact us directly to make changes to your account by emailing: info@purekana.com.

c. Communications: When you sign up for an account or use certain features, you are opting to receive messages from PureKana. You can manage some of your messaging preferences through navigating to account settings or alternatively, you may contact us directly to make changes to your account by emailing: info@purekana.com. Note that you cannot opt out of receiving certain administrative, transactional, or legal messages from PureKana. We may also track your actions in response to the messages you receive from us or through the Service, such as whether you deleted, opened, or forwarded such messages. If you exchange messages with others through the Service, we may store them in order to process and deliver them, allow you to manage them, and we may review and disclose them in connection with investigations related to use of the Service, as well as our efforts to improve the Service. We may not deliver messages that we believe are objectionable, such as spam messages, fraudulent solicitations, or requests to exchange reviews for compensation. If you send or receive messages through the Service via SMS text message, we may log phone numbers, phone carriers, and the date and time that the messages were processed. Carriers may charge recipients for texts that they receive. We may also store information that you provide through communications to us, including from phone calls, letters, emails and other electronic messages, or in person. Our calls with you may be monitored and recorded for quality purposes.

d. Transactions: If you initiate a transaction through the Service, we may collect and store information about you, such as your name, phone number, address, email, and payment information (such as a credit card number and expiration date), as well as any other information you provide to us, in order to process your transaction, send communications about them to you, and populate forms for future transactions. This information may be shared with third parties, and third parties may share such information with us, for the same purposes. When you submit credit card numbers, we encrypt that information using industry standard technology. If you write reviews about products, we may publicly display the fact that you made that acquisition.

e. Activity: We may store information about your use of the Service, such as your search activity, the pages you view, the date and time of your visit. We also may store information that your computer or mobile device may provide to us in connection with your use of the Service, such as your browser type, type of computer or mobile device, browser language, IP address, WiFi information such as SSID, mobile carrier, phone number, unique device identifier, advertising identifier, location (including geolocation, beacon based location, and GPS location), and requested and referring URLs. We may also receive and store your location whenever our mobile applications are running, including when running in the background, if you enable our mobile apps to access such information in the course of using the Service. You may be able to limit or disallow our use of certain location data through your device or browser settings, for example by adjusting the "Location Services" settings for our applications in iOS privacy settings.

f. Different Devices: You may access the Service through different devices (e.g., your mobile phone or desktop computer) and different platforms (e.g., website or mobile app). The information that we collect and store through those different uses may be cross-referenced and combined, and your contributions through one PureKana platform will typically be similarly visible and accessible through all other PureKana platforms.

### **4\. WEB TECHNOLOGIES**

a. Cookies. We, and third parties with whom we partner, may use cookies, web beacons, tags, scripts, local shared objects such as HTML5 and Flash (sometimes called "flash cookies"), advertising identifiers (including mobile identifiers such as Apple’s IDFA or Google’s Advertising ID) and similar technology ("Cookies") in connection with your use of the Service, third party websites, and mobile applications. Cookies may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device, in emails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Service, such as your browser type, search preferences, IP address, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. Cookies may be persistent or stored only during an individual session.

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record keeping purposes. We use cookies on the Website. We may link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information that you submit while on the Website. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when a browser is closed. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on the Website. You can remove the persistent cookies by following the directions provided in your internet browser’s “help” file. If you reject cookies, you may still use the Website but your ability to use some areas of the Website may be limited.

The purposes for which we use Cookies in the Service include:  
Purpose Explanation  
Processes Intended to make the Service work in the way you expect. For example, we use a Cookie that tells us whether you have already signed up for an account.  
Authentication, Security, and Compliance Intended to prevent fraud, protect your data from unauthorized parties, and comply with legal requirements.  
Preferences Intended to remember information about how you prefer the Service to behave and look.  
Notifications Intended to allow or prevent notices of information or options that we think could improve your use of the Service.  
Advertising Intended to make advertising more relevant to users and more valuable to advertisers.  
Analytics Intended to help us understand how visitors use the Service. For example, we use a Cookie that tells us how our search suggestions correlate to your interactions with the search page.  
You can set some Cookie preferences through your device or browser settings, but doing so may affect the functionality of the Service. The method for disabling Cookies may vary by device and browser, but can usually be found in your device or browser preferences or security settings. For example, iOS and Android devices each have settings which are designed to limit forms of ad tracking. For flash cookies, you can manage your privacy settings by clicking here. Please note that changing any of these settings does not prevent the display of certain advertisements to you.

b. Tracking Pixels We employ a software technology called tracking pixels (a/k/a web beacons/web bugs/clear gifs) that enables us to better manage the content on the Website by informing us what content is effective. Tracking pixels are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of visitors to a website. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, tracking pixels are embedded invisibly on website pages and are about the size of the period at the end of a sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by tracking pixels to your personally identifiable information.

We use tracking pixels in our HTML-based e-mails to let us know which e-mails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these e-mails, please see the “Opt Out” section of this Privacy Policy below.

c. Log Files. As is true of most websites, we gather information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Website, to track the movements of users around the Website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

d. Do Not Track. When you use the Website, we may receive “do not track” requests from you, whether via signals from web browsers or other mechanisms. At this time, we do not respond to such “do not track” requests, although we may choose to do so in the future.

e. Security. We take reasonable precautions to protect the confidentiality and security of your personally identifiable information by using industry recognized security safeguards such as site monitoring, secured networks and servers, firewalls and encryption. When we ask for sensitive information, we protect it through the use of encryption during transmission, such as SSL (Secure Socket Layer). Unfortunately, no method of transmission over the Internet is completely secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information within industry standards, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of your personally identifiable information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you. You are responsible for protecting against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer/mobile device. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Our employees are trained and required to safeguard your information. Our internal controls limit access to personally identifiable information based on job functionality.  

f. Communications. Based upon the personally identifiable information that you provide to us, we may send you a welcome e-mail. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide any services you request, to provide newsletters or other updates that you request and to manage your Account. In addition, when you register an Account with us, you may choose to consent to our contacting you by e-mail and to receiving our e-mail subscriptions, editorial e-mails and advertorial e-mails (see below) from us. If, at any time, you no longer want us to contact you by e-mail and/or receive our e-mail subscriptions, editorial e-mails and advertorial e-mails, you may opt out of these functions by changing the preferences in your Account. You can contact customer service by e-mail, telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below to assist you with any such changes to your Account.  
If you have an Account with us, then from time to time, and in addition to e-mails or e-mail subscriptions sent by us, we may send you e-mails that contain advertising or other content sponsored by third party retailers or businesses (“advertorial e-mails”). These advertorial e-mails are clearly marked as such in the subject line and a note at the top of the article itself. The content is paid for by our sponsors and does not reflect the opinions of our editorial staff. If you prefer not to receive these e-mails, you may deactivate your Account or otherwise opt-out as provided in the “Opting Out” section of this Privacy Policy below. We send advertorial e-mails on behalf of the third party sponsors. We do not share your personally identifiable information with such sponsors, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, but we may sell or share aggregate, non-personal information with such sponsors for any legally permissible purpose.

### **5\. THIRD PARTIES**

Our Website may use third parties such as network advertisers to serve advertisements on our Website and may use traffic measurement services to analyze traffic on our Website. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to our Website and other websites you have visited. Third party ad serving enables us to target advertisements to you for products and services in which you might be interested. Our Website’s third party ad network providers, the advertisers, the sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own cookies and other technologies on your computer and track certain behavioral information regarding users of your computer via an IP address or other device identifier. These third party cookies and other technologies are set to, among other things: (a) help deliver advertisements to you that you might be interested in; (b) prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times; and (c) understand the usefulness to you of the advertisements that have been delivered to you. Note that any images (or any other parts of a web page) served by third parties in association with third party cookies may serve as web beacons, which enable third parties to carry out the previously described activities. Third party cookies, web beacons and other third party technologies are governed by each third party’s specific privacy policy, not this one.

Third parties may receive information about you as follows:  

a. Advertisers: We may allow third parties to use Cookies through the Service to collect the same type of information for the same purposes as we do. In doing so, we adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. Third parties may be able to associate the information they collect with other information they have about you from other sources. We do not necessarily have access to or control over the Cookies they use, but you may be able to opt out of some of their practices by visiting the following links: Network Advertising Initiative,Omniture, Digital Advertising Alliance and PrivacyChoice. Please note that opting out does not prevent the display of all advertisements to you. Additionally, we may share non-personally identifiable information from or about you with third parties, such as location data, advertising identifiers, or a cryptographic hash of a common account identifier (such as an email address) to facilitate the display of targeted advertising. You may be able to limit our sharing of some of this information through your mobile device settings, as described above, or through the Service’s settings.

b. Content Partners: We allow third party partners to use and display some of the public content available through the Service, such as your reviews, and other information detailed above.

c. Service Providers: We may rely on third party providers to support or provide some of the services that are available through the Service. We may also rely on third party providers to perform certain services for us in connection with your use of the Service, such as communications and hosting services, network security, technical and customer support, tracking and reporting functions, quality assurance testing, payment processing, our own marketing of the Service, and other functions. We may share information from or about you with these third party providers so that they can perform their services or complete your requests. These third party providers may share information with us that they obtain from or about you in connection with providing their services or completing your requests. Third party providers may also share this information with their subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control. Some of our web pages utilize framing techniques to serve content to you from our third party providers, while preserving the look and feel of the Service. In such cases, please note that the information you provide is being provided to the third party.

d. Aggregate or Anonymous Information: We may share user information in the aggregate with third parties. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertisements. We may also disclose anonymized information about your use on PureKana, for example if you engage in a transaction in connection with PureKana, we may publicly disclose information about the transaction.

e. Business Transfers: We may share information from or about you with our parent companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires PureKana, or all or substantially all of our assets, that company will possess the same information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

f. Investigations and Legal Disclosures: We may investigate and disclose information from or about you if we have a good faith belief that such investigation or disclosure: (a) is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process or law enforcement requests served on us; (b) is helpful to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service; or (c) protects our rights, reputation, property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public. If you flag or otherwise complain to us about content through the Service, we may share the substance of your complaint with the contributor of that content in order to provide an opportunity for the contributor to respond.

g. Links: The Service may link to third party services, like a business’s URL. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with them, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on or applicable to all such third party services.

### **6\. TO OPT OUT OF THIRD-PARTY TRACKING ON OUR WEBSITE USE THE FOLLOWING TOOLS**

You may opt out of the Ad Tech Network by clicking <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/opt-out-interface>

If you would like to opt out of having interest-based information collected during your visits to our Website or other sites, both the National Advertising Initiative (the “NAI”) and the Digital Advertising Alliance (the “DAA”) offer opt out tools to assist you in managing your choices. Click [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1) to visit the NAI opt out page and click <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> for the DAA opt out page.

You may wish to visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/ to learn more about interest-based advertising and your choices regarding having this information used by third parties and your “opt out” choices. Opting out through the DAA or the NAI only means that those DAA or NAI members will no longer be able to deliver targeted content and/or ads to you, which will affect our Website as well as other unaffiliated websites, but does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content and/or ads. Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit these opt out pages, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, your opt out choices may not, or may no longer, be effective.

If you want to be removed from our marketing list and do not want us to send you e-mail, postal mail or other messages about our products and services, you can opt out. To do so, please send an e-mail to info@purekana.com, with the word “REMOVE” in the subject line.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of such residents’ personal information to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please e-mail us at info@purekana.com.

### **7\. CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

Other users may be able to identify you, or associate you with your account, if you include personal information in the content you post publicly. You can reduce the risk of being personally identified by using the Service pseudonymously, though doing so could detract from the credibility of your contributions to the Service.

### **8\. DATA RETENTION AND ACCOUNT TERMINATION**

You can close your account by emailing us at info@purekana.com. We will remove certain public posts from view and/or dissociate them from your account profile, but we may retain information about you for the purposes authorized under this Privacy Policy unless prohibited by law.

### **9\. NO INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM CHILDREN**

The content and services provided by us or our affiliates, sponsors and advertisers are not intended for persons under the age of majority and in no way intended for children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 18 or otherwise not of legal age to form a binding contract in your place of residence, you must have your parent or legal guardian’s permission to use the Website. No information is knowingly collected or retained from children under the age of 13, nor is any such information knowingly used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside the Website. No part of the Website is designed to attract anyone under the age of 13. Children are not eligible to use any services nor may they purchase products provided by us and we ask that children under the age of 13 not submit any personal information to us or visit the Website. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information without parental consent, please contact us directly.

### **10\. SECURITY**

We use various safeguards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### **11\. MANAGE ACCURATE INFORMATION**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer choose to use our services or the Website, you can contact customer service by e-mail, telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below to assist you with changes to your Account. To the extent your Account closes or becomes inactive, we will continue to protect your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### **12\. INTERNATIONAL USERS**

PureKana is primarily based in the United States, with our servers and offices headquartered in the United States. PureKana also maintains servers and an office in the United Kingdom. Please be aware that information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of the Website, an Account, or any services provided by us may be processed and transferred to, and be subject to the laws of, the United States. The privacy and data protection laws in the United States may not be equivalent to similar laws in your country of residence. By using the Website or an Account, or by providing us with your information, you consent to the collection, transfer, storage and processing of information to and within the United States. If our cookies or other software detects IP addresses located in a country outside the United States, we reserve the right to deny access to any and all of our services.

### **13\. CONTACT**

You may contact us concerning our Privacy Policy, or write to us at the following address: PureKana, 6991 E Camelback Rd, Suite 300, Scottsdale, Arizona 85251. Hours: M-F 11am-8pm EST, Info@purekana.com.

### **14\. MODIFICATIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will govern our collection, use, and disclosure of information about you and will be located on this page. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email or by posting a notice on the Service prior to the effective date of the changes. By continuing to access or use the Service after those changes become effective, you acknowledge the revised Privacy Policy.

### **15\. CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS: YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

We do not disclose your personal information to third parties for the purpose of directly marketing their goods or services to you unless you first agree to such disclosure. If you have any questions regarding this policy, or would like to change your preferences, you may contact us at the address listed above.
